http://www.heartratemonitors.com/pages/privacypolicy

Omron
Lifesource (A&D)
Omron
Lifesource (A&D)
We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit this website and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.
This policy applies to information we collect:
On our website.
In phone, email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
When you interact with our advertising and applications we might use on third-party websites and services.
Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it.If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed as acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.
Information We Collect About You and How We Collect ItWe collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:
By which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (”personal information”);
That is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or
About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website, and usage details. We collect this information:
Directly from you when you provide it to us.
Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, and other tracking technologies.
From third parties, for example, our business partners.
Information You Provide to UsThe information we collect on or through our Website may include:
Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website. This includes information provided at the time of subscribing to our service, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, or when you report a problem with our website.
Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
The information we collect automatically is only statistical data and does not include personal information. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:
• Estimate our audience size and usage patterns or supply what we believe is relevant content
Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
Recognize you when you return to our Website. The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:
Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
How We Use Your InformationWe use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:
To present our Website and its contents to you.
To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
"Text Marketing and Notifications:By entering your phone number in the checkout and initializing a purchase, subscribing via our subscription form or a keyword, you agree that we may send you text notifications (for your order, including abandoned cart reminders) and text marketing offers.  You acknowledge that consent is not a condition for any purchase.
If you wish to unsubscribe from receiving text marketing messages and notifications reply with STOP to any mobile message sent from us or use the unsubscribe link we provided you with in any of our messages. You understand and agree that alternative methods of opting out, such as using alternative words or requests will not be accounted as a reasonable means of opting out. Message and data rates may apply.
For any questions please text HELP to the number you received the messages from. You can also contact us for more information. If you wish to opt out please follow the procedures above.”
Disclosure of Your InformationWe may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:
To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. If you place an order with us we may share your personal data with third parties to assist in processing of your order. These may include our webstore, a credit card processor or a shipping company. A full list of our affiliate companies is available by contacting us using the options at the bottom of this page. We always ask that our affiliates not sell our customer data and use it only for it intended purpose.
We may also disclose your personal information to comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. We may use third party applications to provide relevant information and advertising to our visitors. A full list of our affiliate companies is available by contacting us using the options at the bottom of this page. We always ask that our affiliates not sell our customer data and use it only for it intended purpose.
CONSENTWhen you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, or use this website we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason.You understand that we may be required to share this information with third party providers to facilitate the process of fulfilling your order.If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.How do I withdraw my consent?If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use ordisclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at sales@hrmusainc.com or mailing us at:HeartRateMonitorsUSA.com49 Richard Rd Warminster Pennsylvania US 18974Your California Privacy RightsIf you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information. To learn more about your California privacy rights, visit https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/privacy-laws
Notice to European UsersThis Site and the services on this Site are targeted for users in the United States of America. Any information you enter on this Site may be transferred outside of the European Union to the United States of America which does not offer an equivalentlevel of protection to that required in the European Union. In particular, you are advised that the United States of America uses a sectoral model of privacy protection that relies on a mix of legislation, governmental regulation, and self-regulation Article 26 of the European Union’s Data Protection Directive (Directive 95/46/EC, 1995 O.J. (L 281) 31) allows for transfer of personal data from the European Union to a third country if the individual has unambiguously given his consent to the transfer of personal information, regardless of the third country’s level of protection. By using this Site or the services, you consent to the transfer of all such information to the United States of America which may not offer an equivalent level of protection to that required in the European Union and to the processing of that information by the Company on its servers located in the United States of America as described in this Privacy Policy.
Changes to Our Privacy PolicyOur privacy policy is updated at least once a year. An up-to-date active and deliverable email address is needed to receive notice of updates, you may also check back to this page.To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: sales@hrmusainc.comPrivacy Notice for California ResidentsEffective Date: March 2019This Privacy Notice for California Residents supplements the information contained in our privacy policy above and applies solely to all visitors, users, and others who reside in the State of California (”consumers” or “you”). We adopt this notice to comply with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (CCPA) and any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaningwhen used in this notice.Information We CollectOur Website collects information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or device (”personal information”).Category A: IdentifiersExamples: A real name, Internet Protocol address, email address, or other similar identifiers.Collected: YESCategory B: Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)).Examples: A name, signature, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number,passport number, driver’s license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment,employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information,medical information, or health insurance information. Some personal information included in this category may overlap withother categories.Collected: NOCategory C: Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law.Examples: Age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medicalcondition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth andrelated medical conditions), sexual orientation, veteran or military status, genetic information (including familial geneticinformation).Collected: NO
Personal information does not include:
Publicly available information from government records.
De-identified or aggregated consumer information.
Information excluded from the CCPA’s scope, like:
health or medical information covered by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA) and the California Confidentiality of Medical Information Act (CMIA) or clinical trial data;
personal information covered by certain sector-specific privacy laws, including the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FRCA), the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) or California Financial Information Privacy Act (FIPA), and the Driver’s Privacy
Protection Act of 1994.We obtain the categories of personal information listed above from the following categories of sources:
Directly from you. For example, from forms you complete on our website.
Indirectly from you. For example, from observing your actions on our website.
Use of Personal InformationWe may use, or disclose the personal information we collect for one or more of the following business purposes:
To fulfill or meet the reason you provided the information. For example, if you share your name and contact information to request information about our products or services, we will use that personal information to respond to your inquiry. If you provide your personal information to purchase a product or service, we will use that information to process your payment and facilitate delivery. We may also save your information to facilitate new product orders or process returns.
To provide you with support and to respond to your inquiries, including to investigate and address your concerns and monitor and improve our responses.
To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.
As described to you when collecting your personal information or as otherwise set forth in the CCPA.
We will not collect additional categories of personal information or use the personal information we collected for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible purposes without providing you notice.
Sharing Personal InformationWe may disclose your personal information to a third party for a business purpose [or sell your personal information, subjectto your right to opt-out of those sales (see Personal Information Sales Opt-Out and Opt-In Rights)]. When we disclose personal information for a business purpose, we enter a contract that describes the purpose and requires the recipient to both keep that personal information confidential and not use it for any purpose except performing the contract. [The CCPA prohibitsthird parties who purchase the personal information we hold from reselling it unless you have received explicit notice and anopportunity to opt-out of further sales.]
We share your personal information with the following categories of third parties:Order processing, fulfillment and advertising.Disclosures of Personal Information for a Business PurposeIn the preceding twelve (12) months, Company has not disclosed personal information for a business purpose.Sales of Personal InformationIn the preceding twelve (12) months, Company had not sold personal information.
Your Rights and ChoicesThe CCPA provides consumers (California residents) with specific rights regarding their personal information. This sectiondescribes your CCPA rights and explains how to exercise those rights.Access to Specific Information and Data Portability RightsYou have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personalinformation over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will disclose to you:
We do not sell your personal information. We only share your information as needed to process your order. When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address. We may be required to share this information with our partners that assist in order processing and fulfillment.
When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provideus with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system. .
Deletion Request Rights - You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies.
We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service provider(s) to:
Complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform our contract with you.
Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities.
Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise their free speech rights, or exercise another right provided for by law.
Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 et. seq.).
Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when the information’s deletion may likely render impossible or seriously impair the research’s achievement, if you previously provided informed consent.
Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with consumer expectations based on your relationship with us.
Comply with a legal obligation.
Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.
Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion RightsTo exercise the access, data portability, and deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us by sending us a message on our website. Only you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. You may also make a verifiable consumer request on behalf of your minor child.You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. The verifiable consumer request must:
Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative.
Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.
We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you. We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor’s identity or authority to make the request.
Response Timing and FormatWe endeavor to respond to a verifiable consumer request within forty-five (45) days of its receipt. If we require more time (up to [45/90] days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing. We will deliver our written response by mail or electronically, at your option. Any disclosures we provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding the verifiable consumer request’s receipt. The response we provide will also explain the reasons we cannot comply with a request, if applicable. For data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your personal information that is readily useable and should allow you to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance, specifically by electronic mail communication.
Personal Information Sales Opt-Out and Opt-In RightsWe do not sell personal information. We use information only as needed to process your orders or send sale information on our own products if opted in.
Non-DiscriminationWe will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not:
Deny you goods or services.
Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.
Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.
California’s “Shine the Light” law (Civil Code Section § 1798.83) permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketingpurposes. To make such a request, please send us an electronic message through our website or write us at our address listedon our webpage.
Changes to Our Privacy NoticeWe reserve the right to amend this privacy notice at our discretion and at any time. This notice will be updated at least once a year. Your continued use of our Website following the posting of changes constitutes your acceptance of such changes.Contact InformationIf you have any questions or comments about this notice, the ways in which we collect and uses your information described below [and in the Privacy Policy], your choices and rights regarding such use, or wish to exercise your rights under California law, please do not hesitate to contact us as follows:
Via our website: please send us an electronic message through our website using the chat button
Email sales@hrmusainc.com
Write us at our address HRM USA 49 Richard Rd Warminster PA 18974
HRM USA INC.
49 Richard RoadWarminster, PA18974
1-800-403-8285
1-215-259-2700Fax : 215-259-2706sales@hrmusainc.com
About
About Us
Contact Us
Why Shop With Us
Resources
Shopping Cart
Copyright © 2020 HeartRateMonitorsUSA.com.
© 2018 Heart Rate Monitors USA. All Rights Reserved. All trademarks are the property of their respective companies. All prices reflect pricing for purchases within the United States and are in U.S. dollars. Products available while supplies last. Prices subject to change without notice. HRM USA Inc is not responsible for typographical errors. Manufacturer Photo Shop Images may not properly represent actual products featured and after using the products you may never look like the Fitness models representing them.
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
